Today in this webinar,
we're going to look into five key
important parts of your
sales structure that I guarantee
are going to need a little
bit of work.
Those five important structures
are going to be social media,
it's going to be your squeeze pages,
we're going to look at email marketing,
and
we're going to look at landing pages.
And another thing
that we're going to need to look into a
little bit is your
pricing. So to begin with,
we're going to start with social media,
and it's
worth noting that between each one of
those five segments that we're going to go
through today,
we're going to be taking a little break
and a pause.
So please do use
that comment section at the side to ask
all
the questions you need.
I have a very clever little badger named
Luke, who is waiting in the midst
to collate some of the best questions so
that I don't miss them.
So please don't be shy.
We're all friends here.
And if I may be so cheeky to ask,
which I don't do, please subscribe to this
channel. It's a smaller channel
and I'm going to be making content on here
over the
next few weeks and months that's going to
blow your socks off.
I've even hired someone full-time to help
me do it.
So on that, let's begin with social media.
Probably the first part
that we need to talk about.
There's one bit of very terrible advice
which is still doing the rounds, which I
wish would just die out, and that is
that you should be sending cold DMs.
The idea is that sliding into someone's
DMs cold is a good
idea, and it's not.
I actually think it's awful.
So for instance, my barber that I use,
obviously, amazing haircut.
He's busy and he's always busy.
And this shows me
that he's good because if he
wasn't good, he wouldn't be busy.
And I always say to him
that he needs to put his
prices up because I want him to charge
more.
More so that he can have a better life.
But I want him to win,
and I champion all the people
that I use for those
services. However, if I found out
that my barber, Tesh, was
DMing people cold,
"Please come in for a haircut," I'd lose
all
faith in Tesh,
and I probably wouldn't use him because in
his spare time,
I want him to be working on his art
and his craft,
and I want him going on courses
and studying, getting better,
because I want to champion him.
So if you're a personal trainer who's
spending their time sliding into cold DMs,
not only do I think
that coach has shocking marketing,
and if you don't know how to operate the
sales and marketing department of your
business,
how can I expect you to operate any other
parts well either?
If you can't structure your own sales
process,
how can I expect you to be good at
the programming and organization part of
the relationship that we have?
If your marketing is shoddy,
how can we expect your programming to be
excellent? And even if it may be,
it just doesn't add up.
Because if you're hustling in your spare
time sending DMs, you are quiet.
And if you are quiet,
it's because no one
is using your services.
And if no one is using your services,
more often than not, people will think
that you're shit at your job. However,
this isn't the end of
the DM train. It's not like DMs are bad.
And I'll be honest, I could lie here.
The mentorship is a two-way street.
I teach the guys a lot,
but they also teach me back.
I was doing private one-to-ones,
and there's a lad called Sylvester,
and he asks me
if I realize that a company
that I've been using since 2017 called
ManyChat have been acquired by Meta,
Facebook, and Insta.
And this was big news.
So I jumped on a call with a guy
that I was supposed to be
doing a private with,
and he started teaching me about things I
didn't know.
Because you see that chatbot DM
integrations for a long time
were a bit taboo
because we weren't sure
if they'd ruin our reach, our reputation,
or even increase
the chances of our accounts getting
banned.
So I decided to run some tests,
and for about four or five months now,
I've not
had to once say,
"Please click the link in the bio." Last
week, I
got 2,000 leads from chatbots on my
Instagram, Reels, and Facebooks combined.
And if you don't believe me,
I want you all watching this to go try
something right
now.
Head to my personal Instagram page
and DM me the word
offer and you'll see what happens.
I'll give you guys
15, 20 seconds just to give that a go.
Hopefully, the majority of you
are watching this on desktop, and
if you're not, if
you just slide into my DMs,
hit the word offer,
you will then get a message from me.
And the thing is, my phone's here,
so you know that it's not me sending
that. So
a lot of people seem to think that online,
when we say DM us the word, that we've
got staff or we've got people doing it,
and some people actually out there are
paying people money to reply to the DMs.
DMs should not be used manually.
They should be used for automation,
and this is only something that's really
changed in the last few months.
You'll see then as this is happening,
I'm being proactive on the lead
generation side of my business,
and I'm using DMs not to chat to people
cold, but
to nurture the funnel,
which will make more sense in a second.
But we're doing this with automation,
not with manual processes.
And you'll all have an offer that I've
sent you that you can use for 24 hours
from that DM.
And these automations make the processes
of getting people off social media that
little bit easier. You see,
trying to sell to people on social media
is like trying
to talk to someone in a very crowded room.
We want to get people off social media as
fast as possible.
Not to mention,
say you completely forget about this later
and you go, "Oh,
shit,
I need to take James up on his offer,
but I can't find the YouTube video."
You can then go to our DMs and go, "Oh,
I messaged James with
that word. He sent me a link."
So you can get back to it later.
Just imagine that social media
is like having a
chat with someone in a club.
You need to do all the stuff necessary to
get their
number,
and then you just give them a kiss on the
cheek and you leave, knowing that
you can take your time organizing a date
that suits everyone another night.
And I'll move on to
that entire section shortly.
But let's not get distracted.
Let's stay on the subject of social media
for a little bit longer so I can get a
few more questions out of you guys.
Because right now,
as you're watching this,
I want you to think of questions and
challenge me on it.
The next topic we need to cover
is this crazy
theory that you need to be super niched on
social media as a coach or a
business.
And I spoke to one guy recently
that only wanted to coach CEOs.
And I was like, "Hold on, mate. There
are a lot of business owners, even bloody
bricklayers or women
that may own beauty salons that aren't
CEOs that could have the necessary cash to
utilize you as a coach too."
And I have people
that want to work with athletes. I'm like,
"Hold on.
Considering that only 16% of the UK in gym
memberships,
the amount of athletes amongst those
is tiny." Not to mention, if
you're a great athlete You'll have a coach
embedded in your sports club giving you
the S&C that you need. So
when we look at niches,
it's not necessarily
a niche that we need, it's an avatar.
And an avatar isn't the big blue person,
an avatar is the person that we're
speaking to.
And if we know the person
that we're communicating with,
you can communicate with them better.
You'll even notice on TV adverts
that they even talk in the
voice that they're looking to attract.
So let's say you're selling a pickup
truck.
It's like, "Hello,
get down to your local Ford dealership
and have a look at our
pickup trucks." Then
when you're looking at a Bentley
Continental,
"Head down to Bentley."
And actually do you know what?
Bentley don't even do adverts. Porsche,
Ferrari, the most expensive cars don't do
ads. They don't do sales. Let me think.
Like a BMW, Audi might be like,
"And here we have the
Audi SQ8." And they're even talking in the
voice of the
person they want to attract.
"Get down to Ladbrokes
and put on a bet this weekend
for the football." Whereas it's like,
"Welcome to Jo Malone, where we
have scented candles you could buy your
mum." Even the way they talk, the colors.
You can even look at the color palettes on
websites and understand what they're
looking for. But anyway,
you need to know
what your ideal client looks like,
because when you have a good understanding
of
that,
you can create a list of problems
that they face, then you can present the
solutions to them. This
is why in-person trainers have
such an advantage.
They know the problems their clients
are facing because they're
in the trenches interviewing these people
every single day.
So rather than trying to niche down,
try to make sure you're speaking to a
specific person's problems.
You don't need to say, "I only work with
people 22 to 34,
and I only train women." Just have a
set of values and principles
that you work towards.
It's very important
that you understand that, because
if you do not have a specific
tone in which you
are talking about to people,
you're not going to get through.
And even though pickup trucks
are marketed at men,
it doesn't mean a woman can't
walk in and buy one.
Going too niche just makes your life
so much harder, and I can't understand
or fathom the upside.
Now,
the last point I'm going to talk to you
about will really help you grow your
social media and present in a way that's
going to enable you to connect much
better with a colder audience.
I hope you're all here.
Your content is not about you.
I know it's a hard thing
to believe,
and it's a hard reality to get into.
You're like, "Oh,
it's my name on the social media."
But I'll repeat, your content
should not
be about you.
It's always about them. This
was a hard reality for
me. I thought, "Oh,
I'm going to be a creator.
Everyone's going to care what I do."
But have you ever wondered why some
YouTube channels of people doing food
competitions,
seeing how much they can eat,
get so many millions of
views? You got BeardMeatsFood,
Leah Shutkever.
There are loads.
Because every single person watching
that video isn't thinking about them doing
the
food challenge,
it's them thinking about themselves going,
"Could I do that?" Every
bite of the hot dog,
they're there in person going,
"Could I eat this hot dog?"
And think of it this way.
If you saw a creator
and they did a video that
went, "Hey, guys.
Welcome back to the channel.
I want to get in shape for my holiday to
Ibiza this year.
So basically, I
want to be leaner than normal because I've
been struggling with a bit of food.
So what I decided to do
was go into a calorie deficit."
I'm gone. I don't care. I'm like, "Bro,
I don't give a shit about you.
I don't know you." However, if
that very same person was to say,
"If you're someone who's going on holiday
in the next few months and you want to
lose a bit of fat without
over-restricting,
I'll share with you how you could
drop three to five kilograms easily
without having hunger pangs in the
middle of the night.
And to make sure this worked, I
decided to set myself the task of losing
four kilograms in four weeks to
prove that the method I promote actually
works.
Here's the four-step way I did it
that you could implement, too.
Step number one,
implement a calorie deficit."
You see that making your content about
them will eventually make them
care about you. We're humans.
We're all selfish,
and the only things that we do, we
really do for ourselves.
I sponsored something today for $50,000
US,
and I only did it to make myself feel
better about myself.
Even if I feel philanthropic.
Should one day I give a million dollars to
charity,
I want everyone to know because it makes
me feel good.
Even the most selfless of things
is driven out of a desire to please
oneself. When I'm buying everyone dinner,
I'm not even doing it because I like my
friends.
I'm doing it because it makes me feel like
a man.
And when you can understand
that your audience couldn't give a flying
fuck about
you, and only themselves,
can you start to cater
and design content that is
all about them. And when you become
and establish yourself as a professional
problem solver for your audience, well,
then a select few of these
people are going to go,
"If I get all this for free,
I wonder what I'd get if I hired
that person."
So right.
We're going to take a little pause here
because we've gone into a lot of things
about social media there.
We have got four more little modules to go
into.
Now,
I'm going to check what the clever badger
Luke has put
forward as far as questions. Okay,
we've got someone called Haiti.
"The gym manager didn't like the idea of
me wanting to increase my
session prices." This screams to me
that you are going to have a problem
moving
forward.
So your session prices should be
determined by you and not the
gym that you work in. I understand
that some gyms have got funny ways of
doing it.
My first instinct is to get out
and get somewhere where you can,
because your price
as a personal trainer isn't determined by
the environment, it's not driven by the
economy, it's not driven by the postcode,
it's not driven by how much the monthly
rate of the gym is.
It's the demand for your services.
And if you cannot push your rates up
when demand gets high, you are now in a
stranglehold where you can't grow.
It is a very important part of your
business to be able to do so.
So I would say as quick as you can, try to
start looking for other facilities
that are going to respect you as a
trainer.
Because that's what they're doing.
They're caring more about the facility
than they are with you.
Another thing you could do,
if they're not willing to allow you to
charge more for
the hour, charge the same amount
and give people less time.
Because if you're getting busy
and you feel bad
putting your prices up,
if you shorten your sessions from an hour
to 45 minutes,
you get a tremendous advantage.
I actually put my prices up.
All my clients were fine.
I lost one client called Laura.
Still remember her now. She
was a bit of a bitch.
But there was one guy called Russell who,
he was hard. He was a hard man.
He was like 50, and he definitely
had a rough upbringing. But anyway,
Russell just looks me straight in the eye
and
goes, "No, I'm not paying you more."
And I said, "Well,
I'm putting my rates up."
And he was like, "Well,
I'm not paying you more." It
was really awkward, and I
said,
"We'll shorten the session to 45 minutes."
He shook my hand on it.
Now,
shortening the session to 45 minutes meant
I said, "You go do your warm-up,
you come to me ready, and
if we run out of time,
you can go do your arms and
triceps and glutes and delts,
whatever yourself." He was happy, I
was happy.
Amanda CPT,
"Do you recommend posting daily?"
Yes, I think you should. I think
if you can't think of something to post
every
single day,
then potentially you could be in the wrong
job.
But not only that,
you're not going to post every day for the
algorithm.
You're not going to post every day because
it's going to boost your social profile.
You're not going to post every day for any
other reason than you will get a lot
fucking better at this
if you do it every day.
If you're learning to play the guitar,
if you're doing jujitsu,
if you're learning
to surf,
the more often you get on the waves,
get on the mats, or get the guitar in
your hand, you're going to get better.
There is a certain amount of times you
need to do things to get better at it.
Malcolm Gladwell, 10,000 hours of mastery.
The less frequent you post,
the longer it will take you to achieve a
certain
level of competence necessary to do well.
Now, the only reason
that I can look down this camera
and talk in the way that I
talk is because I've done this for so
long. I'm not different to you.
I'm not more skilled than you.
I do not have a fucking bigger brain than
you. I am just repetitions ahead of you.
And the quicker you can understand that,
posting every other day will double the
amount of time
it'll take for you to reach...
And you're not even looking to reach
mastery.
You're just looking to be competent enough
that you can communicate with people,
for them to trust you, and it takes time.
So, that's what I would say.
And Hannah Lee,
"How to start a business as a beginner
working at a local commercial gym
and wants to start online coaching." Okay,
this will probably be the last question we
do on this before we move
on. So,
starting a face-to-face business
is amazing because
you get to understand people's problems.
You get to be with them in person.
Although it's exhausting
and you don't get to work from a laptop in
Bali, trust me,
if it wasn't for those 5,000 hours of
one-to-one that I did in the onset, I
would not have had the knowledge I needed
to be the marketer I am.
So,
when you begin,
you're going to be cheap.
You're going to be cheap because you're
new, and you
should say to people, "Hey,
my name's Hannah, I'm new here.
I'm going to charge less than everyone
else because I have less experience." Now,
you need to talk to everyone in the gym.
You should tell them
that you're a new personal trainer.
You should say, "Look, even
if I just write you a program
and support you,"
whatever it is, get busy.
You should say yes to every single session
you get.
Your calendar is going to be a fucking
disaster.
Come into work, train someone, hour off,
train someone, two hours off, train
someone. Keep going.
You just need to be busy as shit.
You're probably going to be at the gym for
12 to 15 hours a day, but then as you
get busier,
you start to have the power to curate your
sessions a bit.
Okay, not working after 7:00 PM,
not working after 6:00 PM,
not working after 4:00
PM. You can then, over time,
start to bunch up your hours and say,
"Hey,
Trevor, can you come in
and train at this time?" Whatever it is.
We then hopefully will have a period of
the day where you go hard in the morning.
You're probably going to have a gap middle
of the day where you can nap, get your
laptop out, do some work,
have an online strategy, or you can
start to tail off the evening sessions so
you've got some energy.
The biggest mistake you can make
is to be a beginner, to get busy,
and then to
stop ever giving yourself breaks because
some people become such good
coaches,
they never actually have the time, energy,
or effort to create an online
presence. And this social media thing,
this posting online, all of this
is like an
interest savings account. We
are not trying to be famous.
We're not trying to be influencers.
We are putting an hour
or two away a day into a savings account,
which is going to
give us such a bigger return than any
index fund that we can invest in.
We're not going to get taxed on it,
and we're going to be able to build a
relationship.
And you only need a good relationship with
50 or 60 people
to have a very fruition life,
and that's the crazy thing.
Then over time,
you're going to start investing into
that index fund
by putting posts out there,
by creating reels.
And in the onset,
a bit like compounding interest
when it comes to financial
investment,
the first few years you get fuck all,
but then it starts to build up
and you're like, "Holy shit."
And then you start to believe in the
system, then you
start to put more in there.
Before you know it,
you can then start to take dividends from
that.
It is only at that point
when you have a follower size that's
growing, you have an
email list that's growing, and
that you have
a connection with those people,
that you can start to put your services in
front of
them. And it will be 10,000 followers,
1,000 on the email list,
300 end up reading them,
100 people go to the landing page,
4 of them
buy. And it'll be that repetitive process.
But we've got one more question here
before we move into the next bit.
I appreciate how many of you guys
are still listening.
And Daniel Besley says,
"What's more important,
posting consistently
irrespective of quality content, or two,
quality of content directly
targeted at an audience?" Now,
this quality/quantity thing is a
difficult one because I would never say do
a shit post.
But what I would say is,
if you put too much effort into your
individual posts,
they will take long to create.
And imagine this,
if you're learning to box,
you need to try some combinations because
you
need to see those combinations don't work.
You go, "Cool, yeah, jab, cross.
Yep, duck under, hip. Oh, fuck,
that didn't work."
If you put too much effort into your
content and it bombs,
it will really fucking
dishearten you. But
if you make your content good enough to
get a perfect balance
between quality and frequency,
if one bombs, you can course correct.
Similarly, if you were single
and you wanted to chat to girls,
you should go talk
to as many girls as possible,
not hoping that every one
is a perfect approach,
because the ones
that you bomb from will course correct you
better than anything
else.
So you don't want the quality too high
that you cripple yourself, but you don't
want the quality so low
that it doesn't do the thing
that you wanted.
Cool. All right,
we're moving into the next bit.
Clever badger, Luke.
So the next thing from social media
that we need to really address is
squeeze pages. Now,
some people call them lead magnets,
whatever.
I call them a squeeze page because we're
squeezing people of their information.
And one quick thing,
if you haven't DM'd me the word offer,
please do.
And actually,
I am going to pin a link here because I
know some people
said they were going to duck in and out.
There will be a pinned comment on the side
there, which will be there for
you to peruse at any point. Okay,
back to it.
Chatbots have worked amazingly for a lot
of members in my mentorship
recently, and a squeeze page
is a page with unique tasks for you to
get information from someone.
To have a successful squeeze page,
we need to
abide to something called what's in it for
me or WIIFM.
And if we can decide something that's
worth it for them, we can get their email
address.
So when we're looking to come up with
ideas for
people to give us their data,
we need to be creative with it.
A calorie calculator just isn't going to
cut it.
So here's one I could think of.
If you're a CrossFitter who
is sick to death of being beaten by people
in your box
who have quite simply just been training
longer than you, learn how to beat
them in the next WOD by downloading my
32-stage upgrade
program, which is completely free,
and each day for 32 days, you'll get a
set of revolutionary bits of homework to
top CrossFit information
that the top CrossFitters don't want you
to know about.
Another one could be,
one in 1,000 women go into menopause
before 30, one in
100 before 40,
and the rest will head into menopause
around 50.
It's imperative that you fully understand
the physiological and psychological
changes that are going to occur to your
body.
For that reason,
I've created a free menopause guide,
readiness guide that
will send you into immediately
understanding the
process of menopause.
Please provide your best email.
I'll send it across right away.
I'm free balling.
Then I know, welcome to the Man Up course,
and this course is designed for men who
are not hitting their full potential.
Each day over the next 30 days,
you'll be set on a grueling task I hope
that you
don't do, from cold showers,
early morning runs, and even meditating.
Over the next month,
we're going to go through living hell to
achieve two things.
One, to show yourself that you can do it,
and two, to set out to see if you can
graduate from my Man Up course
and to be a good candidate for my
program.
If you can put out something of good
value and propositions in place,
you can do very well.
And you'll note that a lot of the tactics
I use for these very courses, I'm using
with you guys. New chatbots,
already implemented it.
Send your stuff for the offer. Number two,
this webinar is a
squeeze. For what?
Ninety minutes of my time
and to be caffeinated
before bed.
I got over 3,000 email addresses.
What's in it for you?
Well,
even if you don't take me up on my offer,
you're getting a shitload of value.
What's in it for me?
Your contact information.
If we were to run paid ads
or try any other way of getting 3,000
email addresses,
it would cost a bloody fortune.
Not to mention,
only the warmest of these leads
have turned up, the 400 here, which
is amazing.
And again,
if you haven't used the chatbot,
DM me the word offer on my Instagram.
If not, it's pinned here. Do check it out.
It's a heinous discount.
Heinous. Heinous.
I'll pull my pants down for you lot.
And I said paid ads. Foot note,
when it comes to paid ads, don't
send them to a place to buy.
Send them to a squeeze instead.
Think of paid ads as like accidentally
nudging someone in a bar.
Use the opportunity to say hey
and get their number.
Don't use it as a place to try
and take that person home.
"Sorry, I've just spilled my drink on you.
Hey, can I get your number?" "Yeah,
okay." "Oh, sorry,
I spilled my drink on you.
You want to come home?" "Oh, fuck off."
So hopefully,
we'll have rattled some brain cells
surrounding squeeze pages.
So this is going to be a place that's
going to be a good place to stop to do
some
questions. Again, it is our duty on social
media to eventually get people's
information, to get their number,
to take the conversation away from the
busy place of social media so that we
communicate with them.
Let's have a look at some of the questions
that we're
getting.
Kaz Plum. Is that a real name?
I'm not sure.
I get heaps of hits
and watches on my social media Instagram
reels, but no one
actually hits the follow button.
How do you enforce this? Okay.
Some other coaches love to say, "And
if you followed me, and
if you followed me,
and if you followed me." I'm not a massive
fan of that personally.
Now, if people are watching
and they're tuning in,
a lot of the time,
if they watch a lot of that reel,
they're going to be shown your
reels again. Now on YouTube,
people don't have to
follow you for your videos to come up.
You just have to watch their videos.
So sometimes followers can be a vanity
metric because the old model was people
had to follow you to see your content.
Now,
hit and follow isn't going to change your
world. It's not going to change much.
One, if you keep putting out good content,
keep putting out good content,
eventually they should follow. Two,
if you take their email address
through implementing a squeeze
or implementing a chatbot
or doing any of the stuff
that we're doing here, the follows
are irrelevant because the follow isn't
going to
get you paid.
And just because someone follows you
doesn't mean you can contact
them or email them
or send them your latest offer.
If you just tenaciously go after people's
contact information, I guarantee
you 1,000 email addresses will be way more
fruition than 10,000 followers.
So
yeah, you could say,
"If you followed me," whatever,
but it should be done
with tongue in cheek.
It shouldn't be in every one.
For me, it just looks very beggy,
and I don't like that.
I've now got about four million followers,
and I've not had to beg for any of them.
Charlotte Tooth.
Once I've managed to get a load of email
addresses, I struggle to
then get sales afterwards.
Will you cover this?
Yeah,
so we're going to go into this section a
little bit more in this
live. So
one of the great things about having
landing page analytics,
which we're going to
cover in a second, is
when we look at your processes,
if you're getting email
addresses and a lot of people
are reading them and we're not getting the
sales, we
have an offer problem.
We have a conversion problem.
We might have a pricing problem.
Some people are charging too much.
Some people haven't got a clear offer.
Some people have a confusing landing page.
So it could be where you're sending people
from the email.
I guarantee if we
were to clean up your landing page,
which we're going to go into
shortly,
you would get a much better conversion.
And again, this isn't sales tactics.
This isn't forcing people to jump on a
phone call.
This is just making things clear.
So we're kind of jumping ahead of
ourselves, but
we'll get into it.
If you give me a few more minutes of your
time, I will do this
for you.
Nicole, Olympia, Dimitri. These
are fake names, bro.
No one's got a name that cool.
"How do you know you're not giving too
much away?
Where existing clients get annoyed
or people just use you for free
stuff?"
Question of the night. Okay, so
how do you know you're not giving away too
much? Here you go.
I could be concerned
that I'm giving away too much.
I'm actually telling you so much
that I have behind the paid wall in the
mentorship.
I've actually got some of my mentees in
here.
I saw Max before drop a comment. Now,
this is something very important.
The people that are in my mentorship,
when they come on here and they see this,
I don't think they care
that I'm giving away the stuff they paid a
lot of money
for, for free because they get it,
they understand it, and they also
know that you're better off giving away so
much that people go, "Do you know what,
mate?
I'm going to join your program," rather
than keeping it back and keeping it
hidden to the point
that it could hinder your sales.
Here's another thing.
The discount I give you today actually
is less
than what a lot of people in my mentorship
might have paid.
This is another thing altogether.
However,
I don't think I'm going to have many bad
emails after this
Live because the amount of value they get
in the mentorship.
So,
to answer your question,
giving away too much.
I want to give you so much tonight
that you feel like
paying me just to cover this alone,
let alone the course.
And a lot of the time when people pay you,
it's not for the information, it's to
make sure you do it.
Because so many of you will leave this
Live tonight and you'll
do fucking nothing.
But the people that join the course
and pay the amount of money,
they have to make
the money back. If you buy something
and you don't use it, it gives you
this psychological trauma
that you're wasting your money,
that you've worked so
hard for.
The psychological pain of paying me for
the
course is what you need to get the fire
started. Here's something as well.
I wrote an email about this the other day.
I gave my mentorship for free to about 10
or 15 of my friends,
and none of them fucking used it.
I've looked in the back end at the amount
of
modules that they've watched,
and they've done fuck all with it because
they don't
respect it,
because they didn't pay for it.
So think about this.
I can give you so much for free,
but until you pay me,
you're not going to do it
anyway. So people pay you to ensure
that you do
it. The amount you give away on social
is give them everything you can.
Because some people also can't afford you,
and they'll come up to you one day and
go, "Bro, you changed my life.
I never even joined your program."
And you'll feel
okay about it.
As long as you don't go out of business.
People come up to me, they go, "Hey, mate,
you helped me lose 20 kilograms." I'm
like, "Oh,
did you join my academy?" They go,
"Nah." And I'm like, "Do you know
what?
I got a house and a nice car,
I don't care.
It's fine."
Last one here. Mark Sneddon, how are you?
"What kind of followings you need for a
squeeze page or email list to work?" Okay.
Again, we're looking at the wrong metric,
because if you have a big following but
no emails,
it's like being a priest with a massive
cock, right?
So instead of that, when I
had 7,000 Facebook followers,
I quit my gym
because it wasn't profitable for me to go
into the gym anymore.
When I hit 13,000 followers,
I did a seminar in the UK
and had 180 people turn up to it.
So the follower metric's kind of
irrelevant because you might have
5,000 followers, but
if you have 4,000 on your email list,
you could be doing
really well.
So let's not look at the size of
that so much.
Let's just try and make sure
that we've got a nice funnel.
I would say 10% to 20% of your total
following should be on your email list.
If you haven't got 10% to 20% of
that number,
you need to aggressively squeeze your
audience more. Out of those open rates,
I don't really care too much.
I would probably look at a percentage of
people visiting your landing page and then
look at the amount of sales you're getting
from it.
Then looking at the funnel,
we need to address,
have we got a conversion problem?
Have we got an email problem?
Have we got a social problem?
But as long as traffic
is flowing down there,
we should be doing fine.
Okay, last one.
This wouldn't be a good question unless it
was sent here.
Paul Andrews. Max,
I appreciate your comment.
I got a glimpse of that.
"I have 2,000 people in my email list
and email daily.
Get 400 opens with 1 to 10 clicks,
but don't see much by the way of
conversions on my landing page.
Do you offer any advice on upping
conversion
rate?" Yes.
I would.
Primarily,
let's wait till we get into the landing
page thing.
So I'll be honest, in my mentorship,
convenient that I talk about this,
everyone in
there sends me their landing page,
and I go through it, and I'm like,
"Get rid of
this text. This needs to move."
And do you know what?
The majority of the time, people
are paying me $1,000 to go on their
landing page
and go, "Hey, bro, do me a video."
Jayden Lee is our youngest member in the
mentorship. Some of you would've seen him.
He's 17. And
I did a one-to-one with him,
and when I found out his personal story,
I was like, "Bro,
I'm not charging you for this call.
Let's just chat it out, whatever."
And watching a
17-year-old, I'm pretty sure he's 17,
might be 18 now,
doing the stuff he's doing,
and then he did this really good landing
page.
But I actually went on it and I said,
"Sorry, mate,
I want you to do this again."
And I said,
"Just address the elephant in the room."
So Jayden Lee's new landing
page, he goes, "I'm Jayden, I'm young,
I live at home with my
mum, I've got no facial hair.
There's two things you need to know.
One,
I don't charge a lot because I live at
home with my mum.
Two,
one day I'm going to be very expensive,
so this is your opportunity to train
with me before I can't." And he did that,
and he showed me that landing page, and
that was so unique and good for him,
and I have a feeling it'll work.
And
so sometimes you land on people's landing
pages, and it's just something simple
like, "Hey, mate,
put a header video up because this looks
like a fucking scam
page." Or
some of you might follow Jack Hallows,
who's kind of one of Mark
Carroll's graduates with the glute side of
training.
With Jack, I was like, "Mate,
you're such a good character in your
content,
but when I go on your page,
I don't see any of you in the landing
page." I'm like,
"So I've watched hours of your videos.
But then when I go onto your sales page,
there's not one bit of you." So sometimes
it's very simple things like that,
where people just need to be more present
in
their landing pages.
Just having a video where you go, "Hey,
I'm Paul,
this is my gym. I'm a father of two,
husband of one.
I do this, and this
is how I can help you."
And even just saying
something in a landing page like,
"Hey
By the way,
if you don't love the training that I do,
I'm one polite email away
from refunding your money.
You know what I mean?
So let's not jump the gun a little bit.
Again, appreciate you guys on here.
If you haven't DM'd me the word "offer,"
there's a link pinned there.
If you haven't hit like,
you're like already.
Let's get into the next part.
But again, this is great.
Unsubscribe to this channel, you bastards.
So we're going to get into email
marketing.
We're just going to touch on it.
Now,
it's worth saying
that in the next couple of weeks,
I'm adding another course to
the mentorship, which
is a 26-module expansion course of
email marketing.
It's called The Email Advantage.
That's $500 US,
but if you use the offer today,
you get it for free.
Once you're in the mentorship,
all these satellite courses are for free,
and you
get a free IFS ticket
if you sign up today.
But anyway,
email marketing is going to be the best
place to communicate with people.
And I know some of you think it's old
and it's outdated, but it's not.
If anything,
Sunny Webster messaged me the other day
saying, "Emails are back."
Even being able to nudge you about this
webinar is just a place that professional
things can occur.
Paying credit card bills, email.
Plane tickets, email.
If you wanted to ask me anything about the
course, email.
Even after this event,
if you don't buy immediately,
I'm going to email you to follow up.
People that haven't attended the webinar,
the fucking 85% of them,
email.
For my academy, I've written a four
and a half months worth of daily emails,
and
I run a chatbot that gets people to
comment a certain word.
They then get sent to my squeeze page.
Then when they sign up,
they get added to an email automation.
So send email one, wait 24 hours.
Send email two,
wait 24 hours. Send email three,
wait 24 hours.
For years,
I used to write emails every day,
but it became kind of stressful.
I kind of got a little bit over it.
But now I've done this.
Anyone that signs up to my email list gets
hit for four and a half months.
I don't miss a day. I don't break stride.
The automation does all of the work for
me.
Then across almost all of those
businesses, I pitch the business,
give them a
valuable insight, and remain consistent.
If I posted every day for four
and a half months,
would they see every post?
Would they balls? So email is a powerful,
constant variable, which
the best part of is if they're not keen,
they can opt out.
And that's what people are doing
when they unfollow you.
We all go, "Oh, I've been unfollowed.
Oh, I've been unfollowed." People
are just opting out, and that's fine.
It's brilliant, actually. Think of this.
I've got coaches in my mentorship who say,
"I've got 300 people on my
email list,
and I never really use it." And I go,
"Wouldn't it be nice to have
100 people on that same email list where
200 people
have fucked off and unsubscribed,
but at least you got 25 fucking paid
clients
out of it?"
In fact,
all of you should be proactively looking
to shrink your lists,
because as you shrink these lists,
clients pop out, and then
you fuck, my list is small again.
You feel obliged to grow it again.
So again, you just shove people down
that fucking funnel.
Clients pop out, people leave,
go get new people.
So again,
there's a lot of stuff about email
marketing.
So we're going to go into your questions
that you have surrounding email marketing.
But just keep in mind this,
if social media goes down, emails.
If your account gets shadow banned,
emails. If you launch a new product,
emails.
My favorite saying, send emails, get paid.
Send emails, get paid.
If I have a look at the stripe
and we're a little bit low,
my business partner's like, "Yeah,
hit an email out to these lists."
And it's worth noting,
so here's an insight
that I don't really tell
anyone. In the James Smith Academy,
people join, they do a trial, and
then they get segmented into lists.
So I've got current customers
that we can email.
Trialled, never purchased,
get sent into one landing page.
But then people that have been a member
that don't currently have an active
membership get a different email,
and we send them to different things.
For the platforms, before you ask,
I like AWeber for
JSA, Mailchimp for IFS,
Klaviyo for business
mentorship,
and SendGrid I use for JSA as well.
And you're probably thinking your mental
using all four email marketing
platforms, but I like to know the ins
and outs of them because
I'm a bit weird. So let's get into some
questions about email marketing.
Okay. Christopher Wright,
"Even for emails,
what content do you push through
emails?" Good question.
So we want something that's going to be
short,
insightful. We don't want pictures.
We don't want videos.
We want a conversation.
One of the best things you could do
is to look at current trends.
What's happening in the news?
What's my Facebook memories from 10 years
ago?
What film have I watched recently?
I speak about
when Darren and I were in LA,
I got a $500 US laundry bill.
So that's
half the mentorship fee
was for fucking laundry, socks,
and underwear.
But then when it happened, I went,
"This will make a good email." So I wrote
an
email about this.
The only way you could have a worse day
than me is to watch this
email. I watched a bad film last night.
The only way you could waste an hour
and a half is to not join my
program, whatever it is.
But then you can also be there to deliver
value.
You could be like,
"Got in an argument today with a personal
trainer about
progressive overload.
They seem to say this, this, this.
I seem to say this, this, this.
But you know what?
At the end of the day,
we're both kind of right.
The most important thing is
that you're training hard,
following a regime, and you
know what? You could do the same
if you followed my program." So you want
it to be
so that if people were never interested...
Imagine this.
My manager is never going to buy from me.
He's my manager.
He gets 20% of everything I earn.
Everything.
He reads my emails,
and what I don't want
is for one day me to write an email and
him to go, "Nah, can't be bothered.
Can't be bothered." I want there to be
something where even if someone's just
having a shit, they go, "Oh,
James has emailed me.
Wonder what this is about."
If you can get that to the point
that someone could walk past you in the
street and
go, "Christopher, love your emails, mate.
Fist bump." Thank you very much.
I appreciate that.
You have to be creative. And again,
like fitness and growing a muscle,
it's one of those things you're going to
have to train.
It's not going to come easy.
It could take months.
You might be able to get fit enough to run
a marathon before you become comfortable
emailing every day.
Okay, Beyond the Barbell, "What
is the most efficient way to grow an email
list?"
Good squeeze pages.
Good squeeze page campaigns.
So,
one I use for this business mentorship,
"30 Ways in 30 Days."
If you want 30 ways in 30 days to benefit
your fitness business, sign up here.
Then they're getting the value.
Where the fuck did that come from?
I write out 30 emails.
I send them loads of value.
I sell to them in every one.
So if you can give people a reason,
what's in it for me,
we spoke about before, the
WIIFM principle.
If you can convince people
that getting those emails would be of
benefit to them,
they will give it to you. Again,
3,000 emails for this webinar.
Growing the email list,
getting them to opt in.
Gary Clements,
"You say the audience don't give a fuck
about you, but if I've gone
from 20 stone and not active to 15 stone
and in good health, should
or could I promote this on my landing
page?" You could, but here's two problems.
Number one,
of course you did well because it's you,
right?
So
you are financially incentivized. Okay?
Imagine this,
someone says to me, "James, mate,
we're going to run an email marketing
campaign.
You're going to lose 10 kilograms.
We're going to run 10 grand on paid ads.
We're trying to net £350,000." So I go,
"What?
350,000 pounds to lose 10 kilograms?" I
would go borderline eating
disorder for 350 grand because it's my
business.
So when people see you losing five stone,
they're going to go, "Well, this guy's
getting paid to do it." The consumers
and people that you're trying
to appeal to,
they're not financially incentivized to
lose weight.
They've got kids, they've got stress,
and they like getting a sandwich from the
Texaco because they're late for work
or whatever.
So if it's you, there
is a slight problem because of
every PT
gets in shape because they're a PT,
and there's going to be the insinuation
that
it's fine for you. Second thing is, again,
no
offense, but the people following you,
the fact you've lost five stone,
they don't care. What they care about
is that you might actually be able to help
them lose five stone. So it
is about them still.
However, if you can take your story,
and there are a lot of good hooks about
this.
"I'm Gary. I used to be 20 stone,
and I lost five stone
by only doing these four things."
Boom.
"Hi, I'm Gary.
I'm a former fat guy who's lost five stone
and I did it without
tracking calories. This
is how I did it." So your story
is a powerful
hook,
but it's only a powerful hook because it
makes them feel about their
situation. If Gary can lose five stone,
I only want to lose one.
And I know you're British.
Let's change that to kilograms because
it's just going
to sound fucking way better.
Okay.
Tob Protkowinski,
"I've never asked you this in the
mentorship, just thought of
it. I've got a very low follower.
Any tips apart from posting content
frequently?"
To be honest,
let's say I was to say let's run paid ads.
We'd be running paid ads to something
that doesn't work.
We would be polishing a turd.
So I want you to keep posting content
frequently because the low follower count
could be that we're just not
producing content at a value adequate
enough yet, and if we continue with this
endeavor, we should get there. Now,
are there people that post loads of
content and never get anywhere? Sure.
But ultimately,
you should be able to get to some form of
mastery with this.
And so many people feel like they're going
to give up, then they're literally just
a month away from a post that blows up,
grows them 1,000 followers, and then
they're like, okay.
What you might lack at the moment
is belief in yourself,
a strategy that you might just be posting
things like your workouts or whatever it
is.
But outside posting really good content
frequently,
I don't really see what our options would
be, because if you make videos good
enough, they will be shown to loads
and loads of people, and everyone seems to
think it's the algorithm,
that they're using their personal account,
whatever it
is. The truth is,
your content just isn't good enough yet.
Holly, "Do you need to send emails daily
or will it still work weekly?" Okay,
I call this the right time effect.
So Holly, you could do them weekly,
but what
you're looking for
is a reason to do less work. You are.
Because daily is hard.
Daily is stressful. I know, of course.
But when I do my email autoresponder,
"30 ways
in 30 days," sending them every day,
I want to be there in your life every
single
day. I want you to get to 8:00 a.m.
and go,
"Where's my fucking email from James?"
Weekly,
it just seems a bit lazy to me because
people are
impatient for a start,
and anyone can do fucking weekly.
But to get something from someone every
day, they go, "Fuck me, it's only been 23
hours. He's already back.
He's already been creative.
Oh,
that's a clever email." Not to mention,
Holly, your
clients,
one of them is going to get dumped,
one of them is going to have their partner
cheat on them, one of them
is going to get called fat,
one of them isn't going to
get their jeans to fit into them.
Are you really going to wait five
and a half days
before you email them?
Because I know for a fact
that that moment when it happens,
there can only ever be
23 hours and 59 minutes away from me
emailing them again.
And if the button did pop off the jeans,
they would have either just got an email
or they're going to get one the next day.
I don't think you could create an argument
valid enough to say that
weekly was better than daily. So
if weekly isn't better than daily,
then let's do
daily. And I know what you're thinking.
"Oh, but what if there's too much
and some people say
that I'm emailing them too
often?" Well, one,
you can't email too often, you
can only be too boring,
because Instagram you're on it every day,
TikTok
you're on it every day,
emails you check every day.
Can't your emails to people be the same?
You know what I mean?
So I think daily's going to be best,
and if you can make it
good daily, fuck it.
If they're not going to read your emails
every day,
they're probably not going to be a great
client because they're going to be the
client that only checks in with you once a
week.
Okay, last one on emails,
we'll move forward. Kerry Louise Fitness.
"I have 615 online clients." Fucking hell.
Fucking hell. "I'm balancing everything.
I know I need to set up email marketing,
but I'm drowning.
Mum of one, so time is limited."
615 online clients. Yeah.
"I know you need to set up email
marketing." I'd
say what you're doing is working.
If you've got 600 online clients,
Jesus Christ. Wait,
if you've got 600 clients,
you should be making
enough money to jump in the mentorship.
I help you one-to-one.
But I tell you what, even
if you don't do that,
say you're a mum of one, drop me an
email because if you've got a lot of
clients And that's a
problem.
We have a different problem to most people
here.
And Paul Andrews asks,
"Do you offer payment plans on the
mentorship?" We do a
split pay, which you can do.
Whether or not we've got
that on the offer,
check the landing page
that I've sent you to.
But considering that I'm giving it to you
for nearly half price,
yeah, I don't know.
Check the landing page.
Go through to the payment thing.
It's different in different countries,
but if you
do do it, do it through PayPal
or there are other ways.
But we do offer payment plans.
I just don't know.
Because we've discounted it so fucking
heavily, I'm not sure if we could.
Because if you were to buy on a split plan
for this offer and then
take your IFS ticket, I don't know.
I'll have to double-check with the boss.
But we're pretty lenient with payment
plans.
And some people out there charge you what
I charge a month.
We've had some unhappy customers from
somewhere that were charging them eight
grand. Eight grand. The thing is, right,
I'll be honest with you.
I do all right.
I've got a nice house.
I've got a nice car. I'm bored of watches.
I haven't actually got room for another
car.
So I will charge you enough
that I remember your name, but not so much
that I need to be some fucking crazy
wealthy person.
Even the people I can see in the chats
here from the mentorship,
if I charged less
for this, I wouldn't know their names.
I'd be drowning in the Discord every day.
If I charged half what I do for I do,
there'd be twice as many coaches.
If I charged double, which I could,
I would have much better chats with
everyone,
but it would feel like a rip-off.
I'd never want to feel like I'm ripping
people off.
Unless you book a one-to-one with me for
an hour, where I'll fucking, I'll take all
your money,
because I give a lot of energy to those.
You should check the fucking sweat patches
on me come the end of it.
Okay, moving into the next thing.
You should not be doing sales
calls.
You should not be doing sales calls.
You're like, "Oh yeah,
trying to book in a..." No.
Your landing page, right,
which isn't a website,
we need to set little pages up
that we send people to to qualify them.
And this is the best way I can explain
this.
People seem to think they get a sniff of a
sale, let's jump on a call. No.
A waste of your time, waste of energy,
stop it. Imagine this.
Your landing page is as if you are
a restaurant owner, okay?
You've got a restaurant.
You need to get people in it every day,
proactive. You're walking down the street.
There's a cobbled street.
People walk past. It's dinnertime.
They come, and they have a look at a menu.
If they weren't hungry,
they wouldn't be looking at the menu.
So you know they're interested.
If people weren't interested,
they wouldn't be on
your email list. You give them the menu.
Have I got anything I can...
"Here you go, sir. Here's the menu.
Let me know if you have any questions."
Your landing page is like the menu.
They can see what's for offer.
If they see flipping meat and
they're vegetarian, they can go,
and that's fine.
You're not going to try
and convince someone
that doesn't eat meat to come to your
steak restaurant. Again,
they can peruse it. If it's too expensive,
that's fine.
Go somewhere cheaper.
But a lot of the time,
they're not looking.
When you're going out for dinner somewhere
nice in a place that has flipping
cobbled streets,
you're not looking for cheap,
you're looking for good.
You want good.
You don't want to get ripped off,
but you don't want shit food.
You've come out all this way,
put aftershave on,
you've even got your beige chinos
on, okay? They want to know
that they're going to get a good
experience in a
trustworthy place,
that they're not going to sit down for an
hour and go somewhere
else. Your landing page is like the menu.
"Hey, here's everything.
If you have any questions,
let me know." Now,
if people keep asking the same
questions from your landing page,
you probably need to change your landing
page.
But again, course correction.
Then at the end of it,
if they have questions, "Oh,
what's the specials for the day?"
Fantastic.
"Hey, Pablo,
get the fucking specials up there so I
don't have to repeat myself,
because I should be busy out there telling
people to come look at the menu."
If they can't afford it, fine.
If it's not right for them, fine.
But they should qualify themselves.
Now, they might want to go
and look to see what else there is,
and you should let
them. If they walk away, "Oh, come back.
I'll give you 50% off." No.
Let them go look at other restaurants with
shittier menus, with worse staff, in a
worse position, whatever.
They'll come back, they'll eat. "Hey,
welcome back.
Thank you."
This is what you're doing. And again,
the responsibility of an owner of a
restaurant is to take away any
insecurities you
have. "What's the food like?" "Hey,
my friend,
we have the best paella you've ever
seen. Hey, if you don't like the paella,
I'll give you your paella for free, and I
bring my auntie,
and you can slap her in the face.
Come, take a seat,
take a seat." Having
that confidence knowing that your products
and services are so good. "Hey, come on,
my friend.
Best in the street." You make them relax.
"Hey, come on, take a seat there,
pretty lady." Whatever it is,
you should have
some fun with it.
But what you shouldn't do is, "Oh, yeah.
Hi, Steve.
So you've booked a table for six this
Friday at the
restaurant.
Just wanted to spend the next 45 minutes
making sure that we were the
right restaurant for you,
because you'll probably be ending up
spending about
£450.
I know we didn't put the prices on the
menu.
I thought it'd be better to get you on the
phone before we were talking about
prices.
I thought it'd be better to get you on
the..."
No. It's not how it works.
They should come.
They should qualify themselves.
If they have any questions, they can come.
They can always flipping drop you an
email.
If you're a smaller creator,
give them your phone number.
If they try call you, "Who the fuck
are you?
If you have any questions, send me a text.
I'm a busy professional." "Can we jump on
a call?" "No.
If you want to have a sales team for a
high-ticket thing, hire someone and
outsource that." There
is a certain flow
that your landing page is going
to need, like the menu, and this
is my strategy that I usually charge
people money
for.
What you need to tell people
is what it is, what they get, why they
trust you,
why they need it, why to trust you,
how to pay. Okay?
So what is it?
It's online personal training.
What they get.
You get a program,
you get to chat to me around the clock.
I provide you with recipes.
You send me a screenshot of your
MyFitnessPal every
night. What it is. Why they need it.
Let's be honest,
everyone's an online coach.
You need accountability,
someone to check in with, someone
that you actually get on
with,
and someone that's not going to bust your
balls if you missed a workout.
Why should they trust you?
Here's a money-back guarantee.
Here's testimonials from my clients.
How to pay. Boom.
We've been seeing great success in the
mentorship with that, but recently,
putting
in those header videos
that I spoke about before,
where you're just yourself, and
you talk to them.
You make them feel like they're making the
right choice.
Be relaxed and be chilled so they know
they're investing in the right place.
Hey, I'm James. This
is my business mentorship.
I know every personal trainer at the
moment is trying to do this
exact same thing,
but I've learnt a lot over the last 10
years.
I've done some good things,
I've done some bad things,
and I think that I would
like to spend my days helping you with
your problems in Discord.
And if you think there's someone better
else to go, go to their fucking thing.
You know what I mean? So having
that can just disarm people,
and it makes them feel
like you're genuinely involved in the
processes.
Let's get into the questions surrounding
landing pages.
Again,
we can't go into everything because this
is
a webinar. Hopefully, this
is giving you guys some value again.
You got the offer link in there.
You can DM me the word link.
You should subscribe to this page,
or I will fucking fight you.
Caffeine's kicking in, which is great.
8:00 PM here. Great. 8:00 PM.
Georgia Sampson.
"Can't get my online business off the
ground.
I post content every other day.
Is it the quality of what my content
is about?
Posts about results don't get likes,
views, in my experience." Because no one
cares. I'm sorry about this,
but no one cares.
When you post results,
no one cares because it's not them.
If I said to you,
"Hey, here's Tony.
Tony made 100K last month." You're like,
"I don't
fucking know Tony." Right? But if you
were to make a post going,
"Imagine if it was possible to lose 13
kilograms over six months without having
to
give up Smarties and M&M's. Well,
the fact is you can do it
by doing these three things.
And to prove that point,
here's Felicia, and Felicia did it.
She's one of my clients." I don't expect
you to believe that this is a real
transformation. At the end of the day,
I'm a social media creator, but you know
what I mean. You need to present
that in a way. Think about this.
If you see me in an airport wearing a gold
Rolex, you're going to
go, "This guy's a cunt." Right? However,
if you
were to see me in an airport with a gold
watch thinking, "This guy's a cunt." And
then your mate goes, "Oh,
James,
he used to live in a hostel in Sydney
when he first got
here, and he was so skint that
when he first got to Australia,
he could only afford
to spend two nights in a hostel at a time.
So he used to have to go sleep in a bunk
bed in a room with fucking 14 people,
come down, check out,
wait for four hours from 10:00 AM to 2:00
PM
so I could check back into the same dorm
because I didn't have enough cash to my
name at the age of 27 to be able to afford
to stay in it.
Fast-forward a few years,
James managed to write a few books,
has a drinks
business." Whatever it is, you go,
"Fucking hell. He's a legend." I hope.
Now,
the same person in the same place with the
same watch, the only thing
that's changed is the story.
So the reason that people
aren't interested in your results
is there's no story around it.
So that's the important thing here.
Now, people only care about themselves.
You post content every other day.
I would like to know, Georgia, again,
if you can't get your business off the
ground, are you curating the right people?
Are you getting email addresses?
Are you sending them to landing pages?
If you can create a good landing page,
you should make people stupid for
feeling--
If they leave without buying,
almost making them feel stupid.
That's the only Alex Hormozi thing I agree
with, really.
So if I was to vet your business,
I would say there's probably an issue with
socials.
I would love to know how many email
addresses you have.
I'd love to know how often you email them.
I'd love to know how many visitors you get
to a landing page and how many people
are buying.
It's going to be one of the things we've
spoken about.
So Georgia,
I'd love to work with you to get to the
bottom of that.
And again, I'll say this to you.
All of you watching this,
I know some of you are
going to be fucking on the fence.
Imagine this, and I'm not supposed to say
this, but I will.
If you join my mentorship tonight
and in three weeks' time,
you drop me a polite email
and you just go,
"James, mate,
I implemented the things
that you taught me and it didn't work."
You think I'm going to go,
[scoffs] "Good luck?" You think I'm going
to want
someone out there thinking
that my offer was shit? I'd go, "Hey,
do you know what?
I'll refund you.
Next time anyone asks about my course,
just tell them that
it was good." Or whatever it is.
You know what I mean?
Fuck.
There are a lot of people out there you
shouldn't
trust,
but I just don't think I'm one of them.
I never want someone to go, "Oh,
that guy charged my mate fucking 800 quid
and did a runner with it." I'm just not
going to do that. Kate.
"I haven't got an online offering just
yet.
Does the mentorship help with building it,
or do you need to have that organized
already?" No,
we can help you with this because, again,
everyone's so confused about what they
should be selling.
Now, there are a lot of people out there
that just want to use someone online they
like. That's it.
I'm not a better coach than half my
competitors.
I'm not in better shape than half my
I'm not anything special compared to half
my competitors.
But some people go,
"I'm going to be spending £50 a month.
I'm going to spend it with James because I
like him.
I like him because he's open about
snorting cocaine.
He banters and says things
that he shouldn't." Whatever it is.
There are going to be people
that like you,
and it's good just to have something
there that you can do. And even
if you just have five online clients,
it could give
you the cash flow to fuck off your 7:00 PM
person.
You're training someone called Linda at
7:00 PM, you fucking dread the session.
You drag your ass to the gym.
You get a few online clients, you go,
"Do you know
what? Fuck off.
I'm not training after 5:00 PM." So
yeah, we could build something. And again,
Kate,
the first few things I created online
were fucking shite.
I created a fat loss plan that was a PDF.
It was £20 and no one bought it.
No one bought it. I tried giving it away.
No one bought it.
No one even gave me their email for it.
It was terrible.
But only through course correction can we
really figure out what's right.
So yeah. Not loads on landing page one,
so something.
Oh, I don't know what that means. Sorry,
Kate. KH Nutrition.
"Coaching how is the landing page
different to the website?" Okay.
If we go to most personal trainers'
website,
About Me, For Us, Location, Services.
Fuck off.
I don't want to click on all these things.
It's a nice-looking website.
I get to the bottom, YouTube, Twitter,
LinkedIn. Why the fuck?
We've done all this effort to get you from
social media to the website.
You're now on the website
and you're going, oh, Services, About Me.
Then you click on LinkedIn, then you go,
oh, and then you click on another. No.
A landing page is a curated,
nice flow that looks a certain way,
that takes
people on a journey through to buying.
And this is also what's important.
If you have a website,
you might not be getting the analytics
that you need to
determine where the problem is. Because
if you have loads of traffic to a
landing page and no sales,
we have a conversion problem
and we need to look at your
offering.
But if you don't have many people coming
to the landing page and good
amounts of sales,
you have a traffic problem, which
is very different.
Also, landing pages Here's one for you.
Here's a bit of free fucking advice,
you legends.
YouTube just implemented A/B split
thumbnail tests.
So now you upload three YouTube thumbnails
to YouTube, and it will pick the
best one by testing it. And basically,
out of all the people that find
your YouTube videos,
it will present them different thumbnails,
then choose the one
that performs the best. You can do
that with landing pages,
and you've been able to
do that for ages. So KH Nutrition,
when I was
in the office in Sydney with JSA,
I was doing a landing page for one of our
challenges.
I had one with loads of text,
one with not a lot of text,
one with a video.
I thought my sales copy was so good
that the text would do well.
Lo and behold,
we split the traffic through the three
fucking sites.
The video one did way better.
So I made three more videos, 30 seconds,
90 seconds,
and 60 seconds.
Split the traffic between them.
The shortest video did better.
So there's me thinking I can talk to
camera, I know how to sell.
The data on the landing page stipulated
what was real.
We have preconceived notions about what
is going to work and what isn't.
With a good landing page, you can go,
"Wow,
that succinct landing page with a video
and only a bit of text did way better than
the one that had more text."
And you can double down on what works,
and you can
stop doing what doesn't.
Do you understand that if you
were to hire a marketing fucking expert
to come into your business
and teach you this, they would cost
£60,000 a year?
And I've hired marketing people.
They're shit.
They haven't got a fucking clue.
I thought if I paid someone half of what
my salary is, I could get some support.
Turns out, no. So when people are, "Oh,
Leadpages is
expensive as a software to use for a
landing page." Motherfucker, that
is splitting
traffic for you and telling you what works
and what doesn't.
Sorry, the caffeine's kicking in.
Lynette,
"So you seem to be saying rethink of your
website as just a landing page."
No,
a landing page can be completely
different.
A landing page,
you can keep your website if you want,
but I'd rather we send
people to the landing page so we can get
the analytics on what they're doing.
A landing page also doesn't have anything
else to click on.
It just has a nice flow. So when you go to
jamessmith.business,
when you click on that link on this,
or you DM me the word
offer on Instagram,
that takes you to a landing page.
If you keep scrolling,
the story keeps going, and it says, "This,
buy now.
Look at what my test clients say. Buy now.
Look at this." It has one objective to get
people to buy.
Mark Sneddon,
"Is the mentorship helpful if someone
is a complete beginner on all
this stuff? No landing page,
just posting content." It's exactly who
it's for.
So again,
you're not going to be scrutinized.
If you paid me a fucking thousand US
dollars,
I'm going to hold your hand the whole
way. We've got novices,
we've got intermediates,
we've got advanced, we've got
everyone in there. And also,
if you ask a really easy question,
there are people in
there that I've told before
that will help you.
But again, there's nothing
that I won't be willing to help you with.
Dominic,
"Should you write the price on the landing
page instead of making book a
call on the page?" Yes. Again,
let's think of it this way.
The restaurant. You go to a restaurant,
and you do not see
the prices next to the food, you know
that restaurant is going to fuck you.
You know they're going to fuck you in the
arse, right?
Because if the prices are on there,
you should state your prices.
Again, I hate this sales slimy tactic of,
"If we
jump on a call, we can talk pricing." No,
just be
transparent about your fucking prices.
Again, Porsche, Ferrari, they don't go,
"Have a sit down.
We'll tell you how expensive it is." It's
this much.
If you can't buy it, fuck off
and go to Skoda.
It has to be the same.
Because people need to be able to price
themselves in and price themselves out.
Here's the better thing.
If it is expensive, if they go, "Fuck me,
that's a bit more expensive than I
thought," that's a good thing.
I recently got a dog trainer for Alfie.
I messaged him.
He sent me his prices in a PDF.
It was fucking expensive. It
was like $900 for the first three lessons,
and
my first initial thing was, one,
that's expensive. Two, he must be good.
And I booked it. If
that dog trainer said to me, "Hey,
let's jump
on a call and talk about a future for
Alfie," I'd go, "Fuck off, mate.
I'd rather have a dog
that bites kids than fucking sit on a call
with some dog
trainer." So
no, mate,
don't get him on a call because guess
what?
There are really good clients out there.
I would like to think I'm a great client.
When I bought my car, the Audi RS6,
I called them up, I said, "Hey,
you've got two
of these. I'm buying one.
Can I come up?" Cool. Went up.
He said,
"Do you want to test drive it?" I said,
"I've made my mind up.
I just want to buy it." He's like,
"You don't want to know it?" I was like,
"Mate,
just I'll take that one."
People that are good clients don't bust
your balls.
They're not like, "Oh,
can you give me a 3% discount?"
No. Don't get them to jump on a call.
Tell them the prices.
If they can't
get around it,
sorry, mate, if you can't afford it,
go to someone cheaper.
Luke,
"I've just started only one month in
personal training.
I would like to start the mentorship.
I currently don't have a big following
or a landing page.
Would this be a problem
or can I just begin?" Again, these are
options. One, you go, you try it yourself,
you fuck around, you waste time.
But imagine this, right, Luke?
If you're a PT on the gym floor, this
is what you're
saying to people. "Hey,
don't just guess what you're fucking doing
because
everyone is in here guessing what they're
fucking doing.
Here, I give you a structure,
I give you something to follow,
and I give you
support. And when you do that,
you will see progress much better than
other
people." I'm saying the same thing to you
that you're saying to your clients.
Let's cut corners.
Let's not make mistakes.
Let's not waste time and energy
and effort in places we don't need to.
And this is my promise to you.
If you think there's anything missing from
my mentorship, you can email me or tell
me in the Discord,
and I will build it for you.
Whatever you want.
If you go, "James," well, this
is pretty much people have said, "Hey,
can we get
some more information about the fucking
email?" I'll go, "Yeah, let me build you a
whole new course."
The Chatterbox Podcast.
"Where's the best place to make a landing
page?
Don't know where to start." Personally,
I fucking bum
Leadpages. Leadpages website,
I don't get any commission.
I just think it's real simple to use.
My missus uses it.
You can integrate payments.
When people buy, you can email them stuff.
They can host all kinds of different
pages, squeeze.
I just love Leadpages, but again,
I'm biased because it's the one I always
use.
Cerys Louise Fitness.
"I cannot use Discord.
Do not get it one bit." Real simple, okay?
So I never really use Discord.
On the left Are all the different chat
topics.
So right now in the business mentorship,
we've got general, content, BJJ,
YouTube, growing socials, getting leads,
closing clients, retaining clients,
share your business, Q&A,
new module request, IFS Ibiza,
mentorship feedback. Now, those
are all the tabs
that if you have a question,
there's one of it for you.
So you click on that.
"Hey James,
can you take a look at my landing page?"
Cool.
That should be in closing clients.
"Hey James,
can you review my reel on Instagram?"
Cool. That would be in content.
That's it.
There are channels for different topics.
I empty it every day. When
my missus still had stitches in her from
childbirth, I was in the
hospital.
I had my laptop out emptying the Discord.
I can't go to bed at night until I've done
it.
It gives me low-key anxiety
if I don't do it. Okay.
All right.
We're going to move on from this.
So there were some great questions,
fantastic
questions. We're getting near the end.
The last section we're going to look at
is pricing,
which is a fun one.
So these are just going to be some fast
fire things around the pricing that you
might not have even thought about.
So these are like a bonus for you guys for
attending.
Firstly, single session rates.
You never want to sell someone just a
single PT
session.
So the first thing you guys should do
is put your single session rate up.
Even if you charge £40 an hour,
make your single session rate like
80, £90. Make it absurd.
But then say to people, "Oh, it's
£80 for a PT session, but if you buy 10,
I'll do it for 400."
Doing that just positions you
as the most expensive trainer in the gym.
People are going to be like, "Oh my God,
that Steve guy charges £80 an hour.
I can't believe people pay that.
He has so many clients.
He's always so busy." Now,
it's good to position yourself so that
even if no one's ever going to take you up
on a single session, and if someone
goes, "Hey mate,
I just want one session." You go, "Mate,
I wouldn't, it's way too
expensive." So that's an easy hack you can
do.
It will make you stand out to other people
in the gym that's going to make you
think that you're better. Again,
another way to look at your pricing of
being the
most expensive, being better is
if you had an iPhone cable and
you wake up tomorrow,
your alarm doesn't go off, you're like,
"Fuck, holy shit,
what's going on? My alarm didn't go off.
My phone didn't charge." You would then
need to buy a new iPhone cable.
If there was one for £13, one for £4,
one for £3, and one
for £6,
you're buying the most expensive because
it's important to
you. And the type of people
that would buy another cheap cable for £4
you don't
want in your life. And
if you're like a mid-tier PT charging what
everyone else
charges,
they're going to be the same person
that buys the shitty cable twice.
By just getting your single session rate
and putting yourself above everyone else,
they'll perceive you to be the best,
and the people that don't want
that shit to
happen again will use you.
Third thing about pricing is
that your hours are a
commodity. I recommend
that all of you limit,
unless you're in your first maybe--
If you're young and you
fucking just want to get busy,
maybe do 40 hours,
but the majority of you no more
than 30 hours a week.
Think of your sessions like being plane
seats.
So there's only so many seats on the
plane.
The less seats there are,
the more prices go up.
And imagine this,
people seem to think that
the area or the market
or the economy charge what you...
No, it's the demand for your services.
And think of this,
if you want to go to Ibiza,
you know how much it costs.
But if you go on a bank holiday weekend,
you know it costs more. Why? Fuel? No.
Labor? No. Because more people want to go,
and the more people that want something,
the more expensive it gets,
and you're happy to pay it.
Same reason why hotels go fucking crazy on
public holidays, whatever it is.
So how do you get to charge more?
The way that you can get a commodity to
raise in price is by creating demand.
And all of the things we're doing through
socials, emails, all of this is to create
demand because there
is only a finite amount of people
that you can work with on a
daily basis.
I'm going to leave you with two golden
marketing rules
to fuck you for the end of days.
Number one, if you are full
in your business right now, you
are too cheap.
And how do I know you're too cheap?
Because you're full.
If you weren't too cheap,
you wouldn't be full.
Now, if you are not full in your business,
you're not marketing yourself hard
enough. And for the rest of days,
you should be in this dilemma of this
dichotomy
between I'm full, I need to put prices up,
create more demand.
Wow, I'm not full anymore. Wow,
I best fucking get into marketing a bit
more. And this is it. So my barber, again,
to remove it from context, I said
to him, "Hey, mate, you're full.
Raise your prices." He goes, "Oh,
I'll lose
a few clients." I said, "Good." I said,
"Put them up again." He goes,
"I might lose
some more clients." And I said,
"Good." I said,
"Do you know what would be good for
you, Tash?" He goes, "What?" I said,
"An hour with an empty fucking barber
seat." And he goes, "Why?" Because I said,
"When you stare at that seat, you'd
realize the work you need to do on social
media to make sure it's never empty
again."
So here is my closing statement for you
guys.
Just before we go into a super generalized
Q&A where you can ask whatever the fuck
you want, I want to make a point of this.
Let me get comfy.
I don't know if this is true,
but theoretically,
a spaceship must use the majority
of its fuel breaking clear of the
atmosphere.
Once in orbit,
the spaceship can stay there pretty much
forever because it's broken
from the hardest part of the initial
gravity, right?
And the majority is used just in the first
10%, maybe 90% of the
fuel, first 10% of the journey.
And you don't need to get into orbit,
but what you need is to break free from
the
ground. And your first 100 videos
are going to be fucking awful.
By about video 500,
you'll probably find your groove.
It could take you a year to get there,
and that's the truth.
Other gurus online will tell you about
doing paid ads, but if your camera
presence and your ability to talk to
camera is shit and you didn't do the 500
videos, those ads will not perform,
and they will not sell the way that you've
been told to that they would by these
other fucking gurus.
Now, my system,
my mentorship isn't a secret way to
tenfold your revenue.
It's the accountability and reality
that you need to do the
fucking reps.
I tell people inside the mentorship,
"That's not good enough.
Go away and do that better.
This isn't up to scratch.
I expect more of you." Your first four
attempts of landing pages that you put
in there are going to suck.
Your initial ideas for squeeze pages
are going to be
terrible.
The majority of you watching this
are massively
overestimating what you can do in the next
three months.
But at the same time, you
are massively underestimating what you can
accomplish
within the next year.
I could blow smoke up your ass,
but let's look at it this way.
The economic climate right now
is pretty fucking shit.
Everyone's businesses
are down the last seven months.
Everything we are doing right now
is at altitude.
The majority of people
going to the summit
are not going to survive.
And in my mentorship,
we're not thriving and doubling,
tripling our monthly revenues.
We're preparing, we're working,
we're hustling, we're creating
and brainstorming,
so when the climate comes back to what it
should be, we will be the ones in pole
position.
So after all the stuff we've gone through
tonight, if you can think of a better
older brother figure to lead you through
it, then fucking join
their course. And again,
there's going to be a link the whole time
pinned
here.
You can DM me the word offer on Instagram.
It's a one-time offer.
It's not going to be here forever.
I hope a lot of you come to your senses
and join.
Let's get into a general Q&A.
I'm more than happy to answer your
questions.
You should see this. I fucking enjoy this.
I get such a buzz from it.
I feel bad because for so many years I
used to get this buzz out of being a
personal trainer, out of being a coach,
and
it's not that I've lost the buzz,
but you teach someone to back squat
and you get someone to lose five
kilograms,
cool.
But when you can revolutionize someone's
business, the amount of money they
earn, the way they can treat their family,
where they fucking fly their kids on a
plane,
it just fucking makes a big difference.
Matt.
"I've tried a few mentorships,
as you mentioned,
been taken on a ride for far too
much money.
I've asked nicely why certain strategies
haven't been implemented and
why certain steps haven't been taken,
which has left me a fair bit of debt as a
result. I have a one-to-one business.
I'm trying to go online to get out of
that debt, build a business,
and provide for
my partner and newborn.
Can you help?" Matt,
I'll say to you what I say to everyone
else in here.
If you join,
you genuinely put in the effort,
you watch the videos,
and you
show me that you tried something, and
if my strategies don't work, I'll
refund you. I'll just tell you
that because what you want isn't
for me to sell you, it's to know
that you're not wasting money.
And that's what I want to do for you.
I want to say, "Hey, Matt.
Matt Crane, you've got me here on video.
If you genuinely fucking do the work,
I'll refund you." Because
I want to remove any insecurities
that you have.
And again, you've got a partner
and newborn.
I'm not going to fuck you out of more
money, mate.
4Pillar Performance. "Hey, mate.
I haven't backed my price in terms of what
I offer in value, but
do you think there
is a threshold limit from where a
conversion becomes a difficult
one for online purchases from a page?"
I don't know, if I'm honest.
Well,
it depends on how much you're charging.
Is there a threshold? There might be.
It depends on what your services is
and what you're doing, but
this question seems speculative.
You're asking if there's a threshold,
and I don't think you've hit it yet.
As long as people can trust you, right,
and you're not a charlatan, you're not
fraud,
as long as people feel safe with the
purchase, they're fine.
Ed from Film Booth, whose
course I studied, I paid him 10 grand.
Thousand pounds. Never met him.
Never met him.
I just watched his videos and I was like,
"Mate, I want the best
thing that you do." 10,000 pounds.
Fucking great decision.
And there was enough social proof of Ed
online that it made me feel all right
about
it.
Lucia Pretorius.
"Just want to clarify for myself.
I'm newly qualified, go cheaper the rates,
but as soon as I get a couple of years
experience, I should put the prices up,
have a high single session." Okay, Lucia,
what you should do
is pick a very sensible amount of money to
charge
where no one can push back on it.
But your limit is 30 hours.
Never more than 30 hours.
You charge whatever it is,
small amount to get to
30 hours,
but the second you get to 30 hours, boom,
up by 10%, because you can.
You're full.
Now, if someone tries to say to you,
let's say you charge £25 an hour,
which is very moderate. If someone goes,
"Hey,
is it £25 an hour?" You go, "No,
it's £48 an hour,
but I'm currently doing 10 sessions,
one hour for £250.
So you get to save a load of money
if you book 10." If they go,
"I only want one
session," you go, "Cool,
it's £48." You use it so that we
are looking to
set your barrier. This is how much it is.
You get a discount
if you buy a block from me.
But the second you get full,
you keep raising your prices.
Not two years,
because you could get full in two months
if you wanted to, and
you're in the driver's seat of your next
pay rise.
That's what's amazing about owning your
own business.
Maurice Myers. "How do you find ideas,
content to create every day?
Currently a PT,
but feel like I struggle to think of
ideas."
Your clients will ask you things.
It's the best way to do it.
The other day, my brain was numb.
My videographer is also a PT.
I said to him, "Declan,
give me 10 last things your
clients asked you." Boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom. We went and made 10 reels.
I went to my coaches the other day
and I said, "Oh, can all of you give me 10
things that you've been asked?" Your
client's going to ask you questions.
And it will seem crazy to you, Maurice.
They're going to go,
"Do I need to stretch after a workout?"
Boom. Go do your homework.
Go see what Mike Israetel,
Menno Henselmann,
go see what they've all said,
then go, "Are you someone
that thinks you should be stretching after
a workout?
Well, according to an empirical
evidence-based study in 2017,
we shouldn't be doing..." Whatever it is.
Your clients are going to give you so many
amazing ideas for
content.
You've just got to make sure you listen
and write them down.
Ashley.
"Do you work with businesses other than
PT?" That's the way I think
I'll be going, Ashley, if I'm honest.
We've got quite a few businesses in the
mentorship.
I was on a fucking call with a guy called
Jack who sells social
housing. So,
yeah, I will work with any business.
And again, I'll be honest with you,
let's say you have a fucking
dentistry and you join the course
and you go, and this has happened before,
they
go, "James,
this doesn't apply to my business." Boom,
refund, fine.
But I would love to do that.
I reckon in five years' time,
I might have a segment
of the mentorship being PTs
and then work with generalized businesses.
Rory. "This has been fucking mint.
Thank you so much." Thank you for
watching.
Mark.
"I'm thinking about coaching other
personal trainers on how to start off in
the industry.
Would the same principles apply for
scaling and attracting attention
business? Also,
can you tell us about IFS?"
Yeah, it would be. Get in front of them,
create good content.
Same thing. Get their information.
"Hey, if you're a PT
and wondering how to coach people, hey,
if you're new to
personal training, this
is what I'd recommend." "Can you tell us
about IFS?" Okay
So my events team
in 2017 came to me and they said, "Hey,
James, want to run your events?" I said,
"Sweet, cool.
I don't want to do it myself." So they did
my events, all of my
tours, same company.
Then they said to me after I went to
BodyPower,
hated it, said, "This is shit.
It's a fucking shit show." Cool.
They said,
"We're going to do a fitness event.
Will you be happy to help us curate it?"
Cool.
So we do IFS Barcelona, Lisbon, London,
and we've got Ibiza coming up.
So this events team are a team
that do events running a fitness event,
not a
fitness team running in a festival,
whatever it is.
So
IFS, we don't pay the speakers.
Everyone comes just for a fun
weekend.
We've had the Shaun Caseys,
Courtney Black, Stephen Bartlets,
Chris Williamsons.
For this one, you've got the Paul Olemas,
Darren Cartels, myself, the Lucy Lord.
We got some fantastic new speakers.
Shaun Casey was an attendee of IFS who's
now one of our headline speakers.
So for some of you,
you could be coming to IFS,
and you could be speaking in it the
year after. It's a fun weekend.
It's really relaxed.
The ticket you can get from this,
if you join the mentorship tonight, you'll
get emailed an offer for the ticket where
you can come along.
We're just going to hang out the weekend.
We'll have some gin and tonics,
ask me about your business.
The conversation we've had tonight,
we'll do there as well.
If you want payment options,
we can email them to you, by the way.
So
any of you that maybe do want to,
that it's imperative that you
can only buy if you do split pay
or whatever it is,
I'll give you my email address.
And we'll get into the last question now,
which I think is applicable.
Calum MacPherson,
"Do you batch make your content
or make it day by day as it
presents itself?" I try
and make as many good reels as I can in
one go,
but ultimately, I don't like to try
and do too much in a day because it
wears you out, and it wears you out,
and then people can see it in your eyes.
Okay.
Laura Brown,
"I wish I knew this before I bought an IFS
ticket."
We thought this would happen,
so what we'll do is
if you've already bought an IFS
ticket, let us know and we'll upgrade you,
because the upgrade is the same
price as the ticket. So
if you've already got a ticket,
we'll upgrade you to AAA
Boardroom. If you haven't got a ticket,
we'll give you the first initial ticket,
so don't worry. And again,
if some of you are watching this
and you paid full whack
for my course yesterday,
and you can see there's a discount today,
email me. I'll refund you the difference.
Because,
again,
I don't want anyone ever feeling like
they're getting ripped off.
I don't want anyone to feel
that they're not getting the benefit out
of this.
I'm not a charlatan.
I'm not trying to rip you off.
The main thing that I need from you
is for you guys to commit to the course so
we
can start working on your problems.
It's
going to be fucking great.
For any of you that don't know what IFS
is, I've just
posted a link there
that I might have to put the http in front
of.
But
it's an event where pretty much all the
people you follow on social media
are in one place for the weekend.
It's super relaxed.
It's not like they're segregated
or kept separate to you, and we all become
friends, and we all hang out,
and it's good fun.
So there's the post for that.
All right. Very last question.
For the IFS email for you guys,
luke@jamessmith.live
is what you need for the payment plans or
upgrades.
And last question, Dawn,
"I just joined the short-form course
Thursday last
week to try it out before signing up to
the mentorship.
That course, along with this webinar,
is making me realize what I'm missing."
And
Dawn,
if at any point you upgrade to the
mentorship, we will deduct your initial
investment from the course.
Cool. I've really enjoyed this.
Although I'm fucking amped up on caffeine
and got
to go to bed. Guys, please do click
that link, DM me the word offer,
click the link that's pinned here,
jump into the mentorship.
Do it tonight or today if you can.
I won't let you down.
If you do the work,
it's either going to work, and
if it doesn't,
I'm only a polite email away from making
things right.
Appreciate you guys.
Please subscribe to this page.
This has been great.
See you guys in a bit. Bye-bye.